

## **ABOUT**

Experienced analytics professional with a passion for data and technology. In my current role I focus on effectively sourcing, processing, and visualizing data in order to provide insight and actionable intelligence. In my free time I am working on learning more data science tools to expand my current skillset and broaden my knowledge of the field.

## **EDUCATION**

University of Pittsburgh
Bachelor of Science - Business
Administration
Triple Major: Business Information
Systems, Supply Chain Management

## **SKILLS**

Marketing

Tableau Oracle Analytics Cloud

Alteryx (OACs)

Python Oracle Transactional SQL Business Intelligence

VBA (OTBI)

Power BI Google Analytics

Excel Google Tag Manager

### CERTIFICATIONS

Tableau Desktop Certified Associate Alteryx Designer Core Certification Lean Six Sigma Yellow Belt

Please visit my website https://tpoluch.github.io/# (QR code below) for a more thorough understanding of my work and experience



### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Highmark Health, Senior Business Intelligence Analyst May 2022 - Present

- Assisted in the implementation of Oracle Analytics Cloud by setting up and defining the contents of its data housed in the ADW
- Became a SME in Oracle Analytics Cloud and helped define and build new data sources to be used in the tool
- Built management dashboards providing insight into financial operations
- Tools: Oracle Analytics Cloud, Oracle OTBI, Excel, Alteryx, PowerBI

## Highmark Health, Senior Data Reporting Analyst June 2021 - May 2022

- Assisted in the implementation of Oracle ERP by setting up its reporting tool and provided training and support to end users
- Lead the adoption effort of the Oracle Analytics Cloud and built out ETL processes to source and visualize data used by leadership
- Tools: Oracle OTBI, Oracle Analytics Cloud, Excel, PowerBI

## **Highmark Health, Data Reporting Analyst**

#### June 2020 - June 2021

- Use Tableau as a front-end BI tool and Alteryx as a back end data sourcing, processing, and automation tool to design and develop workflows, dashboards, and self-service data
- Tools: Tableau, Alteryx, Python, Excel

## Highmark Health, Emerging Leaders Program Associate *June 2018 - June 2020*

Rotational program consisting of four 6-month rotations in various data analyst roles

- Developed and automated data sourcing, cleaning, and processing infrastructure using Alteryx and Toad for Oracle for team's data needs
- Developed Tableau dashboards visualizing resource forecasted time data, resource availability, resource skills data, and financial and utilization data
- Tools: Alteryx, Tableau, Toad, Power BI, SQL, Excel, VBA, Cognos

## HM Health Solution, Business Technical Analyst May 2017 - June 2018

- Executed agile methodology to aid in team communication, coordination, and planning
- Tools: Agile, Lucid Charts, Jira, Confluence